够了 你这个小淘气
Come on, you... rascal.
这就过分了 噢
Okay, unacceptable! Oh
出什么事了
What is going on?
好吧 啊噢
All right. Uh-oh.
啥叫"啊噢" 那是个啥
"Uh-Oh"? What is that?!
看来Morty的机器人不只是用来打发时间的
Hmm. I think Morty's robot was designed for more than long weekends.
基因编译装置 孵化室
Genetic compiler, incubation chamber.
没错 这是个造娃机
Yep. This, here's some kind of baby maker,
这是个一半Morty一半不知道啥的东西
and that there's half Morty, half who-who knows wh-what?
是我造成的
It's my bad, guys.
我会处理掉的
I'll, I'll take care of it.
- Rick外公  -  不行  - 哇哦
- Grandpa Rick! - No, no! - Whoa whoa whoa!
你这是要干嘛
What do you think you're doing?!
Summer从墨西哥带橄榄回来的时候
Hey, listen. You guys quarantined the house
你们把房子都隔离起来了
when summer brought olives back from Mexico.
这东西说不定能长到特拉华州那么大
I mean, this thing could grow to the size of Delaware.